绝命律师
第一季 第七集
翻译  小七   Liv   寐兮   酸奶
翻译  松   CogitoErgoSum   天青月白
校对  喃喃
时间轴  梦龙  姜姜  今
后期  蜡笔小新的眉毛  8T   虫虫不咬人
总监  喃喃
通缉令
这次也都让我来说
Once again... I do all the talking.
这是唯一可行的方法
That's the only way this works.
拿过来
Hand it over.
在我们交还本子之前
Now, before that happens --
拿过来
Hand it over.
别这样  东西就在我这
No. Hey. I've got it right here.
是这个吗
Is this it?
那应该就是了
I'll -- I will take that as a "Yes."
很好  谜团解开了
Very well. Mystery solved.
我现在就可以拘留你们
You know, I could take you into custody right now,
你个混蛋
You son of a bitch --
你俩都是
both of you.
你干嘛这么说
Where's this coming from?
是你把咖啡倒到我身上的
You're the one who spilled the coffee,
你这个丧尽天良的混蛋律师
you ambulance-chasing piece of shit!
可以稍微冷静一点吗
Can we dial it down, you know, just a notch?
听着  四十五分钟前  我睡得正香
Look, 45 minutes ago, I'm sound asleep.
厄门绍特先生给我打了个电话
I get a call from Mr. Ehrmantraut.
他很担心
He's concerned.
因为你在语音留言里威胁他
He's getting threatening voicemails from you
指控他是个贼
accusing him of petty theft.
我说  "我们可以将问题扼杀在萌芽阶段
I tell him, "Hey, we're gonna nip this in the bud.
不管现在是什么时候
I don't care what the hell time it is.
我们都可以解决这个问题"
We're gonna go talk this thing out."
而就在我们穿过停车场的时候  就刚刚
And walking across the parking lot, just now -- boom --
这本子就好端端地躺在柏油路上
there's a notepad, plain as day, lying on the asphalt,
我只能假设是你不小心掉的  警探先生
where I can only surmise you accidentally dropped it, detective.
我们知道的就这些了
Now, guys, that's -- that's all we know.
听着  老滑头
Let me tell you something, slick --
你就等着我把你弄回费城吧
wait till I get you back to philadelphia.
我不太明白
I'm confused.
宾州难道会因为归还失物
The state of pennsylvania can extradite people
把好人引渡回去吗
for returning lost property?
这法立得不错
That is one bold legislature.
关于里面的东西你有什么想说的吗
Anything you want to say to me about what you found in here?
现在你什么都知道了
Now that it's all out in the open?
也许你儿媳妇
Maybe your daughter-in-law --
也许她会告诉我们的
maybe she's got something to tell me.
也许
Maybe.
也许不会
Maybe not.
等着瞧
Yeah, we'll see.
明天第一件事
First thing tomorrow...
你肯定在想  要是她什么都不知道
I mean, you got to figure she wouldn't reach out to us
怎么会主动联系我们
if she had nothing to say.
希望你所做的一切
Hopefully, whatever you are
不会连累到你的家人
didn't rub off on the rest of your family.
谢谢
Thanks.
不客气  我们离开这个鬼地方吧
You're welcome. Let's get the hell out of here.
"谢谢"的意思是  三个人在这太挤了
No, I mean "thanks" as in "Three's a crowd."
你可以走了
You can go now.
我不在场你不能跟我的委托人说话
You're not talking to my client without me.
他可以  请你走吧
Yeah, he is. Please leave now.
你倒过时差吗
Man. You ever have jet lag?
我现在还在倒
I guess that's what this is.
也许是海拔的原因
Maybe it's the altitude?
可能是海拔
Could be the altitude.
这里海拔一千六百多米  是吧
We're a mile up, right?
那孩子  我很抱歉
Sorry about the kid.
他很年轻  正是大展拳脚的时候
He's young, looking to make his mark.
我喜欢他
I like him.
你儿媳妇  她
Your daughter-in-law -- what --
她会和我们说什么呢
what's she gonna tell us?
我真的不知道
I don't honestly know.
麦克  如果她什么都不说的话
Well, Mike, if she's got nothing to say,
这件事就到此结束了
this pretty well ends it here.
也许你应该在我们找她之前和她聊聊
So maybe you should talk to her before we do.
我和她聊过了
I talked.
我猜  她不会和你们说什么
If I were to guess, I'd say she wouldn't tell you much.
但是
But...
不管怎样  随她吧
Either way, that's up to her.
这是我欠她的
That's the least I owe her.
我们认识的很多人
There's a lot of people we both know
都觉得芬斯基该死
that think that Fensky got what was coming to him --
霍夫曼也是
Hoffman, too.
那整个辖区就像个下水道
That whole precinct was a sewer.
提早退休的人再多一些也不足为奇
Wouldn't be surprised if there's a few more early retirements.
也许是好事  可以补充新鲜血液
Might be a good thing -- new blood.
像那孩子一样
Like the kid.
没错
Yeah.
他还好
He's all right.
就是需要些经验
He's just got to learn, that's all.
有些事情  不要拆穿
Some rocks you don't turn over.
你和他说了什么
What did you say to him?
趁你还记得  逐字逐句复述给我听
Let's go, word for word, verbatim, while it's still fresh.
我说了什么不关你的事
What I said is none of your concern.
只是和一个朋友聊聊
I was speaking to a friend.
你是和一个飞了三千两百公里
You were speaking to a homicide detective
来调查一起双重谋杀案的警探聊天
who flew 2,000 miles to investigate a double murder
而且你还是主要嫌疑人
for which you are clearly the prime suspect.
你怎么会不了解他们的小诡计  心理战
How could you not recognize the mind games, the scams,
还有一出出骗局
the -- the con jobs these people play?
你过去也干过  所以你到底说了什么
You used to be one of them. So what got said?
现在就说  我很认真的
Right now, come on. I'm serious.
我知道你在帮我  但是你不能
I know you're trying to help me, but you can't go --
听着  我是在帮我自己
Look, no, I'm trying to help me.
那两个费城的条子
Those two Philly cheesesteaks --
想把我关在你的隔壁
They want to lock me up right alongside you.
跟我合作  这对我们俩都好
So, work with me here, for the both of us.
你很安全  律师
You're safe, counselor,
我也不再需要你为我服务了
and I no longer require your services.
开什么玩笑
You're -- you're kidding, right?
你认为可以为自己辩护吗
What -- y-you think you're gonna defend yourself?
会有别人去做的
It's in someone else's hands.
-谁  上帝吗  -不
- What -- like god? - No.
别告诉我是哈姆林麦吉尔联合律所
Please don't say Hamlin, Hamlin, Mcgill.
很感谢你的帮忙  回家睡觉去吧
I appreciate your help. Go home. Go to bed.
把账单寄给我
Send me your bill.
我会把账单寄给你的
Oh, I'm sending you my bill.
我会寄...
I'm sending --
肯定会寄的
You better believe it!
是我  善良的送冰人
It's me -- your friendly neighborhood ice man.
培根肉卖断货了
There was a run on bacon.
我下次再给你买
I'll get you next time.
查克  你在吗
Chuck, you there?!
查克
Chuck?
查克  你在楼上吗
Chuck, you up there?
有人吗
Hello?
我在外面
I'm out here!
查克
Chuck?
...112, 113, 114...
老天呐  你在干什么
Holy shit! What are you doing?!
...115, 116, 117,
118, 119...
120  走  进屋去
120! Go! Go! Inside!
你在干什么
What the hell was that?
让我喘口气
Just give me a second.
好了
Okay.
是一项实验  真的
It's an experiment, really.
我正在尝试建立对外界电磁场的耐受性
I've been attempting to build up a tolerance for electromagnetic fields.
-真的吗  -是的
- Seriously? - Yeah.
是的  就好像  你知道的
Yeah, it's like, um, you know,
每天摄入一点毒药  时间一长就有免疫力了
like taking small doses of poison to build up an immunity.
有用吗
Yeah, well, is that a real thing?
因为那听起来好像没用
'Cause that does not sound like a real thing.
真的
It's a real thing.
总之  你也知道的
Anyway, as you well know,
在我家前院西南偏南方向二百米处
there is a 60-kilovolt transformer
有个六十千伏的变压器
200 meters south-southwest of my front yard.
我一直在让自己去适应它
And I've been trying to get acclimated to it.
我今天整整待了两分钟
I got up to two minutes today.
-天呐  查克  -是啊
- Jesus, Chuck. - Yeah.
两天前  我连三十秒都待不上
Two days ago, I could barely stand 30 seconds.
下周我准备尝试五分钟
I'm trying to get up to five minutes by next week.
那真是...
That is just...
可为什么是现在呢
Uh, but why now?
被警察抓走  又被送进医院
Well, after what happened with the police and the hospital,
我现在几乎什么都没有了  吉米
I almost lost everything, Jimmy.
我不能再这样生活下去
I can't go on like this.
我必须想办法好起来
I have to find a way to get better.
我必须好起来  我要回去工作
I've got to. I have to get back to work.
坐在这里  慢慢腐烂...
Sitting here, rotting away --
这不是我该过的生活  谁都不该这样生活
This is no kind of life for me -- for anyone.
我必须重新做回一个有用的人
I need to be useful again.
查克  我真为你骄傲
Chuck... I am so proud of you.
这个过程将会很漫长
It'll be a long process,
但是我坚信自己一定会做到
but one to which I'm very much committed.
我必须做到
I have to be.
天呐  我马上回来
God, I -- I'll be right back.
-我去车里拿点东西  -好的
- I got to get a few more things out of the car. - All right.
很好
All right.
这是什么
What's all this?
只是一些卷宗  办公室里没地方放了
It's just some case files. I'm out of room at the office.
我不想把它们放在车上
I don't want to leave them in the car.
这里有很多敏感信息
There's a lot of sensitive information.
你不会是打算把东西放在这里吧
Y-you're not planning to leave them here.
-是啊  -可能不行  吉米
- Yeah. - I don't know. Jimmy.
不会放太久的  好吗
It'll just be for a little while, okay?
我那里已经堆满了  我都没地方睡觉了
I'm practically sleeping on these things back at my place.
生意那么好吗
Business is that good?
简直太兴隆了  遍地是黄金
It's booming -- streets of gold.
放心  我会尽快把这些东西弄走的
Yeah. I'll get these out of here as quick as I can.
我要为一些遗嘱增添四章十三条的内容
I just need to file the 4-13s on some of these wills,
然后就不会再来打扰你了
and, uh, I'll be out of your hair.
四章十三条
4-13s?
个人财产声明
Personal property statements.
那是五章十三条
You mean 5-13s.
对  抱歉
Yeah. Sorry.
我总跟这些老年人一起工作
I was just working with these seniors.
可能老年痴呆也会传染吧
Maybe the dementia's contagious, huh?
我们说好了  明天老时间见
So, uh, we good here? See you tomorrow. Same time.
我是詹姆斯·麦吉尔
James McGill,
斯科特说会留下801室的钥匙
Scott said he'd leave the keys to 801,
那间出租套房
the suite that's for lease.
给你  看完之后给我就行
Here you go. Just bring them back when you're done.
好的
You got it.
这里看起来  真的很不错
Wow, this is, like... really nice.
怎么听起来那么惊讶
Why do you sound surprised?
不惊讶  不
Not...surprised, no.
只是  你付得起租金吗
Just, you know, could you afford this?
当然了  开什么玩笑
Oh, yeah. Are you kidding?
那些老人对我特别好
Those seniors have been very good to me.
我打算扩大规模  知道吗
I've been meaning to expand, you know?
是时候为自己投资了
It's time to invest in myself.
我觉得这里再适合不过了
Figure this may be just the place.
你不会想念那个美甲店吗
Well, won't you miss the Nail Salon?
我又不是不能回去了
Oh, I can always visit,
说不定还做个法式美甲呢
you know, get some french tips.
这是间清水房
It's a clean slate.
接待处就设在这儿
Put the, uh, reception desk right here.
摆些舒适的沙发给我的委托人坐
Uh, get some comfortable seating for the clients.
真大啊  装得下好多办公室呢
I-it's big -- lot of offices.
是啊  我就喜欢大空间
Yeah, I like the openness.
这样我才觉得呼吸顺畅
I feel like I can breathe in here, you know?
不像那些窄小幽闭的屋子
It's not some claustrophobic, little closet.
闻着一股丙酮的味
That smells like acetone.
这里发展空间很大
Room to grow.
人就是要敢想
Dream big, I say.
大小恰到好处的会议室
Got a decent-size conference room --
虽然没有哈姆林律所那么大  但很舒适
not as big as Hamlin's, but, you know, it's cozy.
我们的老年同胞一定会喜欢的
Our elderly brethren prefer that, I find.
是啊  不过还能搞得再舒适些
Yeah. Could be cozier, though.
你可以弄些刺绣垫子
Maybe you could embroider some little cushions,
织条漂亮桌布
crochet a runner for the table.
-周围摆上摇椅  -没错
- And rocking chairs all around? - Yes.
美国家庭口味连锁餐馆
弄的像老饼干餐馆那样的前厅
Make it look like the front of a Cracker Barrel, huh?
就该这样
Now you're talking.
这是我的办公室
This is me.
真棒啊
I love it.
想要成功就得先看上去成功  对吧
Got to look successful to be successful. Am I right?
没错  看起来是挺成功的
Well, this definitely looks like success.
视野真好
Great view.
在这里摆个宽大的办公桌
Get you a big, fancy desk in here.
要黄檀木桌
Cocobolo desk.
-什么桌  -我也不知道那是什么
- A what? - I don't know what it means,
但我就喜欢说"黄檀木"这三个字
But I just like saying the word "Cocobolo."
好吧  不管是什么桌  都是你应得的
Okay, well, whatever it is, you deserve it.
我还想让你看看这儿
And, uh, I want you to see this one.
就这间
Here we are.
这间比那间好多了
This is way better than the other one.
-是吗  -是啊
- You think? - Uh, yeah.
这是给谁的屋子
Who goes in here?
我要是你  肯定选这间当办公室
'cause I'd be all up in here if I were you.
嗯
Yeah.
这屋子确实不错
Yeah, you know, you're right. It is real nice.
这是转角办公室  你得坐转角办公室
It's a corner office. You got to go with the corner office.
我其实是想把这间留给别人的
Eh, I was saving it for someone.
-给谁  -我的合伙人
- Who? - Well, my partner.
你的合伙人  那是...
Your partner? Who's...
会是谁呢
Who would that be?
你之前不是说对老年法很感兴趣吗
Well, you said you were interested in Elder law.
这...
That's...
这也太...
That is so...
谢谢  真的谢谢你
Thank you. Really.
可我为哈姆林麦吉尔联合律所付出了很多
But you know I've got a lot invested at HHM.
照目前的情况看
With what's going on now,
我非常有可能成为合伙人
I-I'm closer than ever to partner --
也许两年以后  我就是了
Like, maybe two years, and I'm in.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
我只是这样想想而已
Yeah, it's -- it's just a thought.
而且  他们还供我去法律学校读书
Plus, you know, they put me through law school.
我欠他们人情
I feel like I owe them.
实际上我还欠他们钱
Actually, I do owe them -- literally, you know?
不过还是谢谢你想到我  吉米
But it's a nice thought, Jimmy.
你知道的  我就是喜欢胡思乱想
Just, uh, you know, playing with ideas.
多了一间办公室  所以就...
So, I had the extra office and everything, so...
我知道
Yeah. No, I get it. It's...
我想看看厨房
I...want to see the kitchen.
居然是不锈钢的
They have stainless in here.
我家都不是不锈钢
I don't even have stainless at home.
这些话你们可能不想听
I know this is the last thing you want to hear.
但我认为  陪审团不太可能
I think your chances of getting a
给出有利于我们的裁决
favorable ruling from a jury are very slim.
什么意思
What does that mean?
我们没有绝对把握胜诉
We're not in a great position to win at trial.
但我们雇你们
But we came to you people
不就是因为你们说能打赢官司吗
because we were told you win cases.
胜诉并不等于获得有利裁决
Winning doesn't always mean getting a favorable verdict at trial.
每一件案子中  我们都努力帮助委托人
We try to achieve the best possible outcome
取得可能的最好结果
for our clients, given each individual case.
坦白说  我们费尽心思  才让你们免于逮捕
Frankly, we've worked very hard to stave off an arrest.
你们野营的故事造成了些误会
After the misunderstanding about your, uh, camping trip,
地检官认为你们可能是畏罪潜逃
the D.A. was concerned you might be a flight risk.
畏罪潜逃
A flight risk?
可我们只是待在自家后院
We -- we were practically in our own backyard.
我们也是这么告诉地检官的
That's exactly what we told the d.A.
不管怎样  我们已经为二位想出一个
In any case, I think we've managed to come up with a deal
此时最有利的协议
that is very favorable under the circumstances.
协议  我可不喜欢这个词
A deal? I hate that terminology.
1994年前美式橄榄球运动员
辛普森(O.J. Simpson)杀妻一案
他们给辛普森的就是个"协议"
A deal is what they got O.J.
贝茜  也许我们应该
Well, Betsy, maybe we should, you know,
-先听听看  -这词听着就很可怕
- hear it. - I'm just saying, it's terrible term.
那到底是...什么样的"协议"
What kind of...deal?
如果检方要提起诉讼
If the prosecution decides to file,
目前看来这很有可能
which is definitely the direction this seems to be headed,
并且扣给你一堆罪名的话
and if they choose to stack charges,
克雷格  你就得蹲三十年的大牢了
Craig, you're looking at 30 years in prison.
-三十年  -这是最坏的估计  考虑到
- 30 years? - That's the maximum, and given the nature
这些罪名的性质和目前的政治环境
of the charge and the current political environment,
我们应该做好这个准备
I'd say we should expect it.
公众对此类案件的反感会影响裁决
The public outcry in cases like these is a big factor.
不过  我们和地检官进行了几番交涉
However, after much discussion with the D.A.,
他也希望此事越低调越好
who is also invested in keeping the press to a minimum,
于是我们达成了一致
we have arrived at an arrangement,
你要在郡监狱服刑十六个月
which would include 16 months in a county facility.
十六个月
16 months.
比起三十年已经少很多了
Down from 30 years.
你也很有可能提早出狱
And you most likely wouldn't serve all of it.
但他必须认罪
But he would have to say he was guilty.
认罪和恢复县财政这两个条件
Admitting wrongdoing and making the county whole again
帮了很大的忙  所以才给了最低量刑
goes a long way here -- hence the minimal sentence.
什么叫"恢复县财政"
Uh, "Making the county whole again"?
这包括归还160万
It includes the stipulation that you return $1.6 million
挪用的公款
in misappropriated funds.
-把钱还回去  -但根本没有钱
- Give back the money? - But there is no money.
-没有钱  -早就说了  克雷格是无辜的
- There's no money. - We told you -- Craig is innocent.
我理解
I understand.
但是我还是想强调一下
However, I'd like to emphasize again
这个协议是减少克雷格刑期的最好机会
that this deal is Craig's best chance of minimizing jail time.
你是告诉我们
You're telling us
大街上这么多毒贩子和杀人犯
there are drug dealers and murderers walking the streets,
放着他们不抓
but instead of going after them,
偏要把一个无辜的人关起来
they want to put an innocent man in jail.
没有别的办法...了吗
There's no other...way?
不好意思  我觉得目前看来
I'm sorry. I think, under the circumstances,
这是你们最好的选择
this is your best option.
杀人犯和强奸犯就是这样...
Murderers and rapists, and this is how they tr--
好吧  我们没有钱  根本就没有钱
Okay. There is no money. There never was.
你必须在庭审上讲明这一点
You have to take this to trial.
听着  这个选择的确很困难
Look, you have a difficult,
但对你们来说也是最直接的办法了
but nevertheless straightforward choice to make here.
一方面  你们把钱交出来
On one hand, you give up the money,
-认...  -我刚说了  没有钱
- plead... - Ah! I just told you -- there is no money.
认罪  我知道这很痛苦
Plead guilty -- it's painful, I know --
坐一年半的牢
And go to jail for a year and a half.
但其他选择...毫无出路
But your other choice -- that is no choice at all.
如果上庭  很有可能败诉
If you go to trial, you'll most likely lose,
克雷格就得坐几十年的牢
and Craig goes to prison for decades.
你们的孩子只能在探视日去监狱
Your children will grow up seeing their dad through bars
见他们的爸爸
on visiting day.
换我肯定不会犹豫
I know what I'd do.
我会接受协议
I'd take the deal.
两年后  你就能从头再来
Two years from now, you can be starting over.
我知道很困难
It's tough, I know...
但你们不会向困难低头
But you're tough people.
而且你也该为你的家人考虑
And your family is worth it.
我还是让你们俩商量几分钟吧
Why don't I give you a few moments to discuss this?
我知道这个决定很重大
I know it's a big decision.
我们不用商量
We don't need to discuss it.
你被炒了
You're fired.
要不去我的办公室再讨论讨论
How about we go to my office and discuss this?
肯定还有别的办法
I'm sure there's a solution.
没必要
That won't be necessary.
我们不需要你们代理了
We will no longer be requiring your services.
我们真的不是针对你
Yeah, it's not personal, really.
如果你对我们提供的选择不满意
If you're unhappy with what we presented to you,
也许还有别的办法
there may be other directions we can go.
没什么好谈的了  别跟着我们了
We're done here! Please stop following us!
别回头
Don't look back.
只向前看  人生中只向前看
Only look forward. Always in life, look forward.
O70  O70
O-70! O-70!
宾果游戏  游戏者根据叫号描出BINGO图案即胜出
太棒了  人到七十精神爽
Oh, yeah. 70's a good age.
好了  埋头看仔细了
All right, duck your heads,
下一个数字要出炉喽
'cause here comes another number.
N32
N-32.
游戏还在继续
And the action never stops.
要立遗嘱吗  找麦吉尔
希望大家都带了速效救心丸哦
I hope you all took your heart pills,
这实在是太刺激了  对吧
'cause it's almost too much excitement, right?
到底会是哪个数字呢
Which one will it be?
祈祷吧  来了
Say your prayers. Here it comes.
好了  接下来是G48
All right, we've got G-48 --
就是盖伊·伦巴度[小提琴家]的首字母哦
"G," as in "Guy Lombardo."
G48
G-48.
把自个的手管牢了  别动手动脚的
Keep your elbows to yourselves, okay? No body-checking.
下一个是什么呢
All right, what do we have here?
咱们来看看  B6
Wait for it. B-6.
幸运之B6  就像维他命B6
Lucky B-6, just like the vitamin -- all right --
你们要吃的那种
which you should be taking.
让你们的胃肠道健康运动
Keep things moving in the old G.I. Tract.
宾果
Bingo!
有人赢了
Oh, we have a winner!
幸运女神再次降临
Lady luck has struck again.
举起手来  让大家看看
Let's see a hand so we know who's won.
是后面那位可爱的女士
It's the lovely young lady in the back.
恭喜你  女士  你赢得了...
Congratulations, Miss. You've won a, um --
这位可爱的女士赢得了什么
What do we have for the lovely lady?
笔记本
Notebook.
没错  是一本精致的笔记本
Yeah, it's an adorable notebook.
你喜欢猫咪吗  贵姓...
Do you like cats, Miss, uh...
艾琳  我爱猫咪
Oh, Irene. I love kitties.
我养了两只暹罗猫  奥斯卡和费利克斯
I have two Siamese cats -- Oscar and Felix.
费利克斯会给自己洗澡
Felix can wash himself.
奥斯卡不行  它...就是不行
Oscar won't. He -- he just won't.
多么有趣啊  谢谢你
What a lovely story. Thank you.
你能把这个给艾琳吗
Um, can you take that to Irene?
你回来了帮我顶一下  行吗
And when you come back, cover -- yeah?
我要休息一小会
Uh, I'm gonna take a short break,
有人需要我提供法律援助
'cause somebody needs legal help.
詹姆斯·麦吉尔先生办公室
Offices of James McGill,
请问您要找谁
Esquire. How may I direct your call?
好的  好的  没问题  请稍等
Yes. Yes, of course. Um, one moment, please.
又见面了
Déjàvu. Hello, again.
-很高兴见到你们  -你好
- Good to see you. - Nice to see you.
有什么需要我帮忙的吗
So, how may I be of service?
我们想雇你当我们的律师  麦吉尔先生
Well, we would like to hire you as our attorney, Mr. McGill.
真的吗
Wow. Really?
但是我们有一些条件
However, we have certain conditions,
你必须接受
and these are not up for debate.
我们不想坐牢  完全不想
We want no jail time -- zero.
克雷格是清白的  我们希望你能证明
Craig is innocent, and we expect you to prove that.
我们不想再让他的名声遭到如此诽谤
We won't see his name smeared like this any longer.
能先别着急吗
Um, can we back up just a scooch?
上次你们还非常肯定
'Cause last time we spoke, you were very enthusiastic --
坚持要委托哈姆林麦吉尔联合律所
you were positively insistent about being represented by HHM.
没事  不用加
Well, uh... That's all right.
我们意见不合
We've parted ways.
为什么呢
May I ask why?
我们不同意他们的辩护策略
We...disagreed with their defense strategy.
好吧
Okay.
他们当我们是罪犯
They treated us like we were guilty.
之前拒绝我为你们代理  而现在...
So, your previous objections to my representing you are now...
抱歉  上次是我没想清楚
Oh, I'm sorry about my bluntness at our last encounter.
很不幸
Unfortunate.
没错  但我们
Yeah, I -- but we really --
我们对此非常抱歉
we're very sorry about that.
我们深思熟虑过后
We thought long and hard about it,
我们...
and, um, we...
考虑到你的热情
And, you know, given your passion
和你敢于挑战的态度
and your can-do attitude... mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
我们真心
...we really --
-相信你就是我们的律师  -没错
- We just believe that you're the lawyer for us. - For us, yes.
这么说真是抬举我
Well, as flattered as I am by this,
但自从上次以后
um, since we last spoke,
我转变了主攻领域
I've changed my area of specialization,
现在专注于老年法
so I concentrate on Elder law now.
但你说过会全力帮我们
But, I mean, you said that you would fight for us.
没错  你当时...相当坚定
Yeah, you... you were -- you were adamant.
你答应过帮我们拿到无罪判决
You promised to get us a not-guilty verdict.
我不是这么答应的
I don't think I exactly promised that.
你说我们会是头号委托人
You said we would be client number one,
全天候待命
morning, noon, or night, and --
没错  我当时是认真的
Yes, and I meant what I said, at the time,
但是今非昔比
But times change.
但我们已经付了预付金
But we've already paid you a retainer.
没错  预付金
Right. A retainer.
你们就这么叫吧
That is what you called it.
这是你们律师的术语
That was your specific terminology.
抱歉我失陪一下
It -- could you excuse me for a moment?
我憋了很久了
I, uh, had a big gulp on the way over.
你好
Hey, there.
有意思
Funny story.
我再次找到了属于你的东西
I found something that belongs to you -- again.
-是吗  是什么  -是"谁"
- Yeah? What? - "Who?"
想象一下弗兰德夫妇主演《第25小时》
Picture "The 25th Hour,” starring Ned and Maude Flanders.
《辛普森一家》的角色
天  凯特尔曼夫妇吗
Oh, christ. The Kettlemans?
今天还流失了其他客户吗
You lose any other clients today?
没错
Yeah.
疯子先生和太太
Mr. And Mrs. Cuckoo Bananas
把辩护的肥差给了我
just offered me the plum job of defending them.
他们去找你了
They came to you?
可不是嘛
Yeah, I know.
我不清楚你怎么惹毛了他们
I don't know what you did to piss them off,
但肯定不得了
but it must have been good.
他们说了什么
W-What did they tell you?
没说什么  只说了你
Not much, just, uh, that you treated them
-把他们当罪犯  -天哪
- like they were guilty. - Jesus.
吉米  我知道...
Look, Jimmy...I know...
这样要求很过分
I know this is a lot to ask,
但你得说服他们回我们律所
but you have to convince them to come back to HHM.
-是吗  -没错
- I Do, Huh? - Yes.
求你了  这很重要
Please. It's important.
-你觉得值吗  -吉米  我没说笑
- What's it worth to you? - Jimmy, I'm serious.
他们离开是因为他们觉得能打赢官司
They left because they think they can win this case,
但他们赢不了
but they can't.
根本没什么有利因素
I managed to scrape together --
我东拼西凑才提出一个协议
from practically nothing, I might add --
他们应该感到幸运才是
a deal they should feel lucky to have.
这才是最有希望的办法
This is their absolute best bet.
求你了...
Please...
告诉他们  回来是更好的选择
make them understand it's better for them if they come back.
跟我说说这协议
Tell me about this deal.
老年法
Elder law?
我不知道他什么意思
I don't know what that is.
我也不知道
Yeah, me neither.
老年  你觉得...
Elder. Do you think...
也许如果我们老了...
Maybe if we were old --
久等
Sorry. Whoo! Oh.
膀胱到底能装多少呢
The mysteries of the bladder. Right?
所以怎么说
So, how do we get started?
要签那份合同吗
Do you need us to sign that little paper?
我感到非常抱歉
I am -- I am very sorry,
但我恐怕接不了你们的案子
but I'm afraid I can't take your case.
我的日程排得满满当当
My schedule is just -- it's just chock-full right now.
强烈建议你们回哈姆林麦吉尔联合律所
I highly encourage you to go back to HHM.
我确定他们会非常欢迎你们
I'm certain they would welcome you with open arms.
不  我们不回去
No, we're not going back there.
跟他们...合不来
They were... incompatible.
我懂
I understand.
他们让你们面对残酷的现实
They asked you to face some harsh realities,
我理解  没人喜欢
and I get it -- no one likes that.
但最重要的是金·韦克斯勒是个好律师
But bottom line here -- Kim Wexler is a fine attorney.
她和地方检察官关系很好
She has a great relationship with the D.A.
虽然我很想自吹自擂
Much as I'd love to sing my own praises,
但我很可能搞不定
I doubt I could get you a deal
比她更好的协议
as good as the one she already has.
我们不想要"协议"
Okay, we don't want a deal.
我们希望你  我们的律师  还他清白
We want you, our lawyer, to exonerate Craig.
"还他清白"
"Exonerate"?
有点言过其实了
That is, uh -- that is a big word,
特别是你们这个官司
particularly in your case.
我们不会接受什么协议
Yeah, there will be no deal.
我们根本没贪  谈什么协议
There is no money with which to make a deal.
我们不要再自欺欺人了好吗
We -- can we all three just parachute down from cloud cuckoo land?
因为我们心知肚明  钱是有的
'Cause we know, without question, there is money.
-不  没有  -我清楚地记得为了这袋钱
- No, there... - I distinctly remember a spirited game
我们曾激烈地拔河呢
of tug-of-war over this money,
这笔钱我们讨论了好久
Money which we then discussed at length.
你找了很多借口
You made many excuses
来为这笔钱辩护
justifying your possession of said money.
钱是有的
It's there. It exists.
拜托  我快要疯了...
S-shh. Now, just, please, for my own sanity...
你们不可能把一大袋钱藏一辈子
You can't hide a big bag of cash forever,
也肯定花不了其中的一分钱
and you certainly will never be able to spend any of it.
所以还是回律所  向韦克斯勒小姐道歉
So, go back to HHM, apologize to Ms. Wexler,
然后接受那个协议
and for Christ's sakes, take the deal.
如果真有钱的话
If there were any money --
女士  够了
Lady, enough!
如果真有钱的话
If there were any money,
那就要进行全面结算
there would have to be a full accounting of it.
每一分钱都要拿出来
Every penny would have to be present --
每一分钱
Every single penny.
你懂了吧
You understand?
全部
All of it.
包括给你那三万...
That includes the $30,000 that you --
-克雷格  他懂了  -好吧  他懂了
- Craig, yes, he gets it. - Okay. Yeah, he gets it.
不管发生什么  麦吉尔先生
We're in this together, Mr. McGill...
我们是一条船上的
Come what may.
现在我们怎么办
Now where do we begin?
你要的凯特尔曼的卷宗  全在这儿了
There you go. Kettleman -- that's all of it.
金呢
Where's Kim?
她搬到东翼去了
We moved her over to the east wing.
东翼  玉米地那边
The east wing? That's the cornfield.
为什么把她搬到玉米地那边  霍华德
Why are you sending her to the cornfield, Howard?
以前从没这么叫过
Never heard it called that before.
你就是这么叫的
Well, that's what you call it.
你要惩罚她
You gonna punish her
就因为你失去了那对精神错乱的客户
just 'cause you lost those two batshit Kettlemans?
你看我一点都没有因为
You notice I'm not exactly crowing over
挖走了你的客户而洋洋得意
how I snaked them away from you.
吉米  这是你要的卷宗
Jimmy, here are your files.
我懒得跟你讨论我的员工政策
I'm not gonna discuss my employee policies with you.
我还需要人来帮忙
I'm gonna need some help here.
是啊...
Yeah...
的确如此
You sure are.
那个混蛋要开除你吗
That prick firing you?
最佳情况也是  我的两年计划
Best-case scenario is my 2-year plan
现在变成十年计划了
iust became a 10-year plan.
那个蠢货  你没做错什么
That schmuck. You didn't do anything wrong.
-我丢客户了  -不是你的错
- I lost the client. - Not your fault.
他们已经神志不清了
They're not really playing with a full deck --
凯特尔曼两口子
Those Kettlemans.
你要接他们的案子
You had to take their case?
对不起  我试过了  我真尽力了
I'm sorry, okay? I tried. I r-- I really did.
我有点强人所难了  你当然尽力了
I'm not being fair. Of course you tried.
他们想怎么做是他们的事
They'll do what they want to do.
希望你没有对他们夸下海口
Hope you didn't promise them too much.
我不相信你能做得
I doubt you'll be able to do more for them
比我们律所还好
than we were offering.
你对我的实力评价很高嘛
You think very highly of my skills, obviously.
不是这个意思  吉米  这个官司输定了
It's not that, Jimmy. It's a loser case.
那个协议是他们最好的机会了
That deal was their best chance.
我累死累活跟地检官兜圈子
After I worked my ass off finagling with the D.A.,
结果呢...  算了
and it's just like... whatever.
肯定还是有办法的  对吧
There's got to be a way, you know?
-待我上了庭...  -你输定了
- I take it to court... - You'll lose.
凯特尔曼连如何销毁证据都不会
Kettleman did a terrible job covering his tracks.
首先
For starters,
他开了大量虚假开支的支票
they've got reams of checks he wrote for false expenses.
我只能眼巴巴看着它们被归为证据
And I can't even challenge their admission into evidence
因为那是他开给自己的
because he wrote them to himself.
我知道我们绝不能承认委托人是有罪的
I know we're never supposed to say our clients are guilty,
但是  反正也不是我的委托人了
but, hey, not my client anymore --
他罪不可赦
He's guilty as sin.
好吧  但是应该有办法...
Yeah, but there has to be something --
-有什么漏洞或者  -反正我找不出了
- Some loophole or... - None that I could find.
一定有什么办法的
There has to be a way.
吐钱就有办法
Not without the money.
这是凯特尔曼夫妇唯一的筹码了
It's the only chip those Kettlemans have,
而他们却不接受
and they refuse to play it.
挪用公款
在今晚的第二局中
And Anderson leads things off
安德森做首击球员
in the top of the second inning here tonight.
第一投  曲线球未击中
First pitch -- curve ball for a strike.
比分0比1
Count is 0-1.
本来有些担心
There was some concern
今晚会有小雨
that we'd have some light showers,
不过看起来是杞人忧天了
but it looks like it's gonna be clear tonight.
-是的  -一个坏球  1比1
- Absolutely. - That's a ball. 1-1.
天
No.
奥特纳尔准备好了
Ortner readies.
投球  是一记直奔右中场空区的直线球
Throws, and it is a liner toward the gap in right-center field.
罗伯茨开始跑了  接球...
Roberts on the run, reaches out...
接到球了
And makes the grab.
这样第二局就领先一分了
And that puts one away here in the second inning.
下一个上场的是总是令人印象深刻的李
Next up, the always imposing Lee.
这个赛季他有个不错的开始
And he's had a great start this season.
天呐  每次看都觉得更多了
Jesus. Gets bigger every time I look at it.
感谢您没有卷款潜逃
Thanks for not heading to the Bahamas with this.
你在做什么呢
What are you doing?
"正确的事情"
"The right thing."
你知道要去哪里吗
You know where you're going?
是的
Yeah.
所以我们两清了吗
Am I correct in assuming we're now square?
两清了
Square.
早上好
Good morning.
是谁来了  克雷格
Who is it, Craig?
是麦吉尔先生
Oh,it's Mr. McGil!
早上好  快请进吧
Good morning. Come on in.
我很喜欢你们的布置
Oh, I love what you've done with the place.
我上次来的时候  这里还不能去竞争
Last time I was here, it was, uh, well, not a contender
《好管家》杂志的封面呢
for the cover of Good Housekeeping --
那是肯定的
that's for sure.
你有关于我们案件的进展了吗
Do you have news about our case?
实际上  我有
I do, in fact.
但是在我们直击核心之前
But before we get to the nitty-gritty,
我们应该先谈谈你们的协议
I think we should chat about your deal.
我们告诉过你了  不接受协议
We told you -- there will be no deal.
你确实说过了
You did, didn't you?
但是  现在情况有变
However, circumstances have changed.
什么情况
What circumstances?
为了回答这个问题
To answer that, um,
我能建议你们先去检查下那些钱吗
might I suggest that you go check on that money
就是你坚持说没有贪的那些
you insist you didn't take?
在楼上浴室的水池下面
In the upstairs bathroom, under the sink?
等等  你是怎么
Wait. How could you...
贝茜
Betsy!
不  不  不
No! No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no! No!
没事的  贝茜  肯定是...
It's okay. It's okay, betsy. It's got to be...
不  它们肯定在这里的
No. It's got to be in there somewhere.
你把它怎么了
What did you do with it?
"它"指的是...
By "It," You mean...
钱在哪里
Where is it?!
你是指钱啊  让我想想
You mean the money. Uh, let me see.
它已经在路上了
Uh, it's, uh, on its way
快到地检官的桌子上了吧
to the D.A.'s desk right about now.
什么  你  你个小偷
What? You -- oh, you thief!
彼此彼此
Takes one to know one, doesn't it?
是他拿的吗  你是怎么偷走的
He took it? How did you take it?
一个好的魔术师从来不会揭晓自己的秘密
A good magician never reveals his secrets.
好了  接下来我们要这么做
Now, here's what we're gonna do.
不需要你来告诉我们怎么做
Oh, you don't tell us what to do.
你偷了我们的钱
You stole from us.
我们会让警察逮捕你的
We'll -- we will have you arrested.
看得出你很生气
I-I can see how upset you are, and,
但即使是在你清醒的时候
even on a good day,
你也毫无逻辑...
you and logic are...
你刚说要逮捕我
But think about what you just said.
罪犯可没法让警察逮捕别人
Criminals have no recourse.
而你们两个就是彻头彻尾的罪犯
And you two -- you're criminals, big-time.
你竟敢
How dare you?
幸运的是  你们那聪明绝顶的律师
Luckily, you have a very talented lawyer
已经找到了方法
who has found a way to minimize the damage
将伤害降到最低
you've brought upon yourselves.
你已经被炒了
Oh, you're fired.
我已经辞职了  我说的是金·韦克斯勒
Oh, I quit already. No, I'm talking about Kim Wexler.
现在你们要回去找她
Now, you're gonna go back to her,
为之前草率地终止她的代理
you're gonna apologize for your hasty decision
向她道歉
to terminate her services,
你们要接受她的好意  接受那份协议
And you're gonna fall on her mercy and take that deal.
我们会说出你收我们贿赂的事情
We'll tell... about the bribe you took.
你可以那么做  当然可以
You could do that. You absolutely could.
那样我就会陷入麻烦
And I'd be in a mess of trouble --
大麻烦
A real pickle...
但是你也一样  凯特尔曼夫人
But so would you, Mrs. Kettleman.
因为现在只有凯特尔曼先生
Cause right now, only Mr. Kettleman is on the hook
被资产挪用这件烂事套牢了
for the whole embezzlement kerfuffle.
但是贿赂  怎么又把它叫做贿赂了
But the bribe -- w-we're back to calling it a bribe? --
这个也会影响到你的
Yeah, that implicates you, as well.
不会的
It does not.
-全都是我做的  -并不是
- It was all me. - No, it wasn't.
我保证会告诉大家的
I'll make sure everyone knows that.
往好的方面想想
Look on the bright side, you know?
也许他们会想出
They could work out some kind of
监狱间夫妻互相探视的项目
inter-prison visitation program, the occasional conjugal.
也许也不算太糟糕
Maybe it won't be all bad.
你也许还能组织自己的帮派呢
You -- you'll probably wind up running your own gang.
你们要知道
Thing you folks need to know about me --
我已经一无所有了
I got nothing to lose.
天啊  可惜了我那漂亮的办公室
Christ, you should see my office.
-不  还没有结束  -结束了
- No, it's not over. - Yeah.
我们再去找个律师
Let's find another lawyer.
-好了  贝茜  -不  不
- Come on, betsy. - No, no.
不  我们不能容忍这样
No. We don't have to put up with this.
我绝不能受到这样的对待
I will not be treated this way.
贝茜  还有孩子们
Betsy...the kids.
孩子们
The...
我们必须要这么做
We have to do this...
为了我们的孩子
For the kids.
他们不能同时失去我们两个
They can't lose us both.
我们必须要这样做
We have to.
不
No.
会没事的
It's okay.
都会好的
多谢了
Thank you.
詹姆斯·麦吉尔法律办公室
Law offices of James M. McGill.
请问找哪位
How may I direct your call?